

# KUDZAYI BAMHARE

EMAIL: KUDZAYIBAMHARE@GMAIL.COM

LINKEDIN:

HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/KUDZAYI -BAMHARE-3B6991B7/

GITHUB: HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/KUDZMAT

## **ABOUT**

I am a versatile and entrepreneurialminded professional with a unique blend of experience in marketing, entrepreneurship, and software development. I enjoy work which alllows me to exercise my creativity, solve problems and make an impact to the people we are serving.

### **OPEN SOURCE WORK**

- The Software Carpentry Certified Instructor and contributor
- CHAOSS Africa open source community member and contributor

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### STANFORD'S CODE IN PLACE

Section Leader | 2023

 As a section leader for Code in Place, a free, online programming course offered by Stanford University, I mentored a group of approximately 15 students on a weekly basis. I led virtual discussion sessions to reinforce key concepts and served as a resource for students to ask questions and seek guidance. Additionally, I collaborated with fellow section leaders to ensure a consistent and high-quality experience for all Code in Place students, and actively participated in professional development opportunities to enhance my own knowledge and teaching skills.

### **LUCIDITY TRADING COMPANY**

Tech Lead and Founder | 2020 - PRESENT

 Lucidity Trading Company is a company I founded that deals with the wholesale trading of hardware products in Zimbabwe. My role within the company is managing the company's finances, engaging and maintaining relationships with clients and partners, and finding ways to grow the business while mitigating risks. I am also responsible for the development and maintenance of the business app, built in Python, which tracks our performance on a monthly basis.

#### SAMANSCO INDUSTRIES

Marketing & Research Analyst / Digital Media Manager | 2017 - 2020

 As digital media manager, my responsibility was developing and executing strategies to promote the company's brand and content across multiple digital platforms. I mainly oversaw the creation and implementation of digital marketing campaigns, managed social media channels, and website development, analyzed and reported on the performance of digital campaigns, and collaborated with external creative teams to develop content.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **HYPERIONDEV**

Sept 2021 - April 2022

• Software Engineering Bootcamp

#### UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN

January 2016 - Dec 2016

Post-graduate Diploma in Management Studies, Specialising in Marketing

**January 2012 - Dec 2015** 

 Bachelor of Social Sciences Majoring in International Relations and Industrial Sociology